<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Reyound</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="credit_card_detail">Your credit card details are securely\nencrypted and passed directly to our PCI IDSS\n compliant Payment Gatway for processing.\n We only store your credit card last 4\n digits and the expiration date. Your traffic\n to this page is secured using a 256-bit SSL\ncertificate</string>
    <string name="uh_oh_you_have_no_orders">Uh, oh you have no orders</string>
    <string name="my_orders">My Orders</string>
    <string name="contact"><b>Write to us</b>\n\ndrop us a line and we will get back to you, as fast as we can email us at</string>
    <string name="facebook"><b>Facebook us</b>\n\nConnect with us on your favourite social network</string>
    <string name="tweet"><b>Tweet us</b>\n\nReach out in140 characters! we are at Reyound store</string>
    <string name="talk_to_us"><b>Talk to us</b>\n\nMonday to Sunday10:00AM to 10PM call us on 9876543210</string>
    <string name="reyound">Reyound is a E-commerce App/website for all lifestyle products.We provide shoppers all over India with good expansion on its portal it brings latest affordable products as per your choice at the lowest price.</string>
    <string name="delivery"><b>Free Shipping</b>\n\nWe Provide Free Shipping on all our product.</string>
    <string name="gifts"><b>Weekly Gifts Members</b>\n\nWe are your one-stop shop for nationwide online store.</string>
    <string name="money"><b>Money Back Guarantee</b>\n\nStart saving straight away with discount offer on items.</string>
    <string name="support"><b>24/7 Support</b>\n\nWe work for all customer to make satisfied shoppers value.</string>
    <string name="privacy">Reyound Privacy Policy\nThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from Reyound.com (the Site)\nPERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT\n\nWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as Device Information.\nWe collect Device Information using the following technologies:\n– Cookies are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies
– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.</string>

    <string name="shipping"><b>Shipping Policy</b>\n\nReyound (“we” and “us”) is the operator of (https://Reyound.com) (“Website”). By placing an order through this Website you will be agreeing to the terms below. These are provided to ensure both parties are aware of and agree upon this arrangement to mutually protect and set expectations on our service.\n\n<b>1. General</b>\n\n Subject to stock availability. We try to maintain accurate stock counts on our website but from time-to-time there may be a stock discrepancy and we will not be able to fulfill all your items at time of purchase. In this instance, we will fulfill the available products to you, and contact you about whether you would prefer to await restocking of the back-ordered item or if you would prefer for us to process a refund.\n\n<b>2. Shipping Costs</b>\n\nWe provide Free Shipping for all Products. Incase of Shipping Fees Charged, shipping costs are calculated during checkout based on weight, dimensions and destination of the items in the order. Payment for shipping will be collected with the purchase.
        This price will be the final price for shipping cost to the customer.\n\n<b>3. Returns</b>\n\n<b>3.1 Return Due To Change Of Mind</b>\n\nReyound will happily accept returns due to change of mind as long as a request to return is received by us within 15 days of receipt of item and are returned to us in original packaging, unused and in resellable condition.\nReturn shipping will be paid at the customers expense and will be required to arrange their own shipping.
Once returns are received and accepted, refunds will be processed to store credit for a future purchase. We will notify you once this has been completed through email.
        (Reyound) will refund the value of the goods returned but will NOT refund the value of any shipping paid.\n\n<b>4.1 Transit Time Domestically</b>\n\nIn general, domestic shipments are in transit for 2 – 7 days\n\n<b>4.2 Transit time Internationally</b>\n\nGenerally, orders shipped internationally are in transit for 4 – 22 days. This varies greatly depending on the courier you have selected. We are able to offer a more specific estimate when you are choosing your courier at checkout.\n\n<b>4.3 Dispatch Time</b>\n\nOrders are usually dispatched within 2 business days of payment of order\nOur warehouse operates on Monday – Friday during standard business hours, except on national holidays at which time the warehouse will be closed. In these instances, we take steps to ensure shipment delays will be kept to a minimum.\n\n<b>4.4 Change Of Delivery Address</b>\n\nFor change of delivery address requests, we are able to change the address at any time before the order has been dispatched.\n\n<b>4.5 P.O. Box Shipping</b>\n\nReyound will ship to P.O. box addresses using postal services only. We are unable to offer couriers services to these locations.\n\n<b>4.6 Military Address Shipping</b>\n\nWe are able to ship to military addresses using USPS. We are unable to offer this service using courier services.\n\n<b>4.7 Items Out Of Stock</b>\n\nIf an item is out of stock, we will wait for the item to be available before dispatching your order. Existing items in the order will be reserved while we await this item.
        \n\n<b>4.8 Delivery Time Exceeded</b>\n\nIf delivery time has exceeded the forecasted time, please contact us so that we can conduct an investigation.
        \n\n<b>5. Tracking Notifications</b>\n\nUpon dispatch, customers will receive a tracking link from which they will be able to follow the progress of their shipment based on the latest updates made available by the shipping provider.\n\n<b>6. Parcels Damaged In Transit</b>\n\nIf you find a parcel is damaged in-transit, if possible, please reject the parcel from the courier and get in touch with our customer service. If the parcel has been delivered without you being present, please contact customer service with next steps.\n\n<b>7. Duties and Taxes</b>\n\n<b>7.1 Sales Tax</b>\n\nSales tax has already been applied to the price of the goods as displayed on the website\n\n<b>7.2 Import Duties and Taxes</b>\n\nImport duties and taxes for international shipments may be liable to be paid upon arrival in destination country. This varies by country, and Reyound encourage you to be aware of these potential costs before placing an order with us.\nIf you refuse to to pay duties and taxes upon arrival at your destination country, the goods will be returned to Reyound at the customers expense, and the customer will receive a refund for the value of goods paid, minus the cost of the return shipping. The cost of the initial shipping will not be refunded.\n\n<b>8. Cancellations</b>\n\nIf you change your mind before you have received your order, we are able to accept cancellations at any time before the order has been dispatched. If an order
        \nhas already been dispatched, please refer to our refund policy.\n\n<b>9. Insurance</b>\n\nParcels are insured for loss and damage up to the value as stated by the courier.\n\n<b>9.1 Process for parcel damaged in-transit</b>\n\nWe will process a refund or replacement as soon as the courier has completed their investigation into the claim.
        \n\n<b>9.2 Process for parcel lost in-transit</b>\n\nWe will process a refund or replacement as soon as the courier has conducted an investigation and deemed the parcel lost.
        \n\n<b>10. Customer service</b>\n\nFor all customer service inquiries, please email us at info@reyound.com</string>

    <string name="Return"><b>Return Policy</b>\n\nRETURNS\n\nOur policy lasts 15 days. If 15 days have gone by since your purchase, unfortunately we can’t offer you a refund or exchange.\n\nTo be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the same condition that you received it. It must also be in the original packaging.\n\nTo be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the same condition that you received it. It must also be in the original packaging.
        \n\nSeveral types of goods are exempt from being returned. Perishable goods such as food, flowers, newspapers or magazines cannot be returned. We also do not accept products that are intimate or sanitary goods, hazardous materials, or flammable liquids or gases.\n\nAdditional non-returnable items:\n* Gift cards\n\nTo complete your return, we require a receipt or proof of purchase.
         \n\nRefunds (if applicable)\nOnce your return is received and inspected, we will send you an email to notify you that we have received your returned item. We will also notify you of the approval or rejection of your refund.\nIf you are approved, then your refund will be processed, and a credit will automatically be applied to your credit card or original method of payment, within a certain amount of days.
         \nLate or missing refunds (if applicable)\nIf you haven’t received a refund yet, first check your bank account again.
          \nThen contact your credit card company, it may take some time before your refund is officially posted.
           \nNext contact your bank. There is often some processing time before a refund is posted.\nIf you’ve done all of this and you still have not received your refund yet, please contact us at info@reyound.com.\n\nSale items (if applicable)\nOnly regular priced items may be refunded, unfortunately sale items cannot be refunded.
        \n\nExchanges (if applicable)\nWe only replace items if they are defective or damaged. If you need to exchange it for the same item, send us an email at info@reyound.com and send your item to: Saibaba Nagar, 90 Feet Road, Near Himalaya Hotel, Mumbai, MH, 400017, India.\n\nGifts\nIf the item was marked as a gift when purchased and shipped directly to you, you’ll receive a gift credit for the value of your return. Once the returned item is received, a gift certificate will be mailed to you.\n\nIf the item wasn’t marked as a gift when purchased, or the gift giver had the order shipped to themselves to give to you later, we will send a refund to the gift giver and he will find out about your return.\n\nShipping\nTo return your product, you should mail your product to: Saibaba Nagar, 90 Feet Road, Near Himalaya Hotel, Mumbai, MH, 400017, India.
        \n\nYou will be responsible for paying for your own shipping costs for returning your item. Shipping costs are non-refundable. If you receive a refund, the cost of return shipping will be deducted from your refund.\n\nDepending on where you live, the time it may take for your exchanged product to reach you, may vary.\n\nIf you are shipping an item over INR 1000, you should consider using a trackable shipping service or purchasing shipping insurance. We don’t guarantee that we will receive your returned item.
</string>

    <string name="Terms"><b>Terms And Condition</b>\n\nTERMS OF SERVICE\n\nOVERVIEW\n\nThis website is operated by Reyound. Throughout the site, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to Reyound. Reyound offers this website, including all information, tools and services available from this site to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here.\n\nBy visiting our site and/ or purchasing something from us, you engage in our “Service” and agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions (“Terms of Service”, “Terms”), including those additional terms and conditions and policies referenced herein and/or available by hyperlink. These Terms of Service apply to all users of the site, including without limitation users who are browsers, vendors, customers, merchants, and/ or contributors of content.\n\nPlease read these Terms of Service carefully before accessing or using our website. By accessing or using any part of the site, you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this agreement, then you may not access the website or use any services. If these Terms of Service are considered an offer, acceptance is expressly limited to these Terms of Service.
     \n\nAny new features or tools which are added to the current store shall also be subject to the Terms of Service. You can review the most current version of the Terms of Service at any time on this page. We reserve the right to update, change or replace any part of these Terms of Service by posting updates and/or changes to our website. It is your responsibility to check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to the website following the posting of any changes constitutes acceptance of those changes.\n\nSECTION 1 – ONLINE STORE TERMS
     \n\nBy agreeing to these Terms of Service, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.\n\nYou may not use our products for any illegal or unauthorized purpose nor may you, in the use of the Service, violate any laws in your jurisdiction (including but not limited to copyright laws).\n\nYou agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit any portion of the Service, use of the Service, or access to the Service or any contact on the website through which the service is provided, without express written permission by us.
     \n\nYou must not transmit any worms or viruses or any code of a destructive nature.\n\nA breach or violation of any of the Terms will result in an immediate termination of your Services.\n\nSECTION 2 – GENERAL CONDITIONS
    \n\nWe reserve the right to refuse service to anyone for any reason at any time.\n\nYou understand that your content (not including credit card information), may be transferred unencrypted and involve (a) transmissions over various networks; and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices. Credit card information is always encrypted during transfer over networks.\n\nThe headings used in this agreement are included for convenience only and will not limit or otherwise affect these Terms.\n\nThis site may contain certain historical information. Historical information, necessarily, is not current and is provided for your reference only. We reserve the right to modify the contents of this site at any time, but we have no obligation to update any information on our site. You agree that it is your responsibility to monitor changes to our site.
    \n\nSECTION 3 – ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS AND TIMELINESS OF INFORMATION\n\nWe are not responsible if information made available on this site is not accurate, complete or current. The material on this site is provided for general information only and should not be relied upon or used as the sole basis for making decisions without consulting primary, more accurate, more complete or more timely sources of information. Any reliance on the material on this site is at your own risk.\n\nSECTION 4 – MODIFICATIONS TO THE SERVICE AND PRICES
     \n\nSECTION 4 – MODIFICATIONS TO THE SERVICE AND PRICES\n\nPrices for our products are subject to change without notice.\n\nWe reserve the right at any time to modify or discontinue the Service (or any part or content thereof) without notice at any time.\n\nWe shall not be liable to you or to any third-party for any modification, price change, suspension or discontinuance of the Service.\n\nSECTION 5 – PRODUCTS OR SERVICES (if applicable)\n\nCertain products or services may be available exclusively online through the website. These products or services may have limited quantities and are subject to return or exchange only according to our Return Policy.\n\nWe have made every effort to display as accurately as possible the colors and images of our products that appear at the store. We cannot guarantee that your computer monitor’s display of any color will be accurate.\n\nWe reserve the right, but are not obligated, to limit the sales of our products or Services to any person, geographic region or jurisdiction. We may exercise this right on a case-by-case basis. We reserve the right to limit the quantities of any products or services that we offer. All descriptions of products or product pricing are subject to change at anytime without notice, at the sole discretion of us. We reserve the right to discontinue any product at any time. Any offer for any product or service made on this site is void where prohibited.
    \n\nWe do not warrant that the quality of any products, services, information, or other material purchased or obtained by you will meet your expectations, or that any errors in the Service will be corrected.\n\nSECTION 6 – ACCURACY OF BILLING AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION\n\nWe reserve the right to refuse any order you place with us. We may, in our sole discretion, limit or cancel quantities purchased per person, per household or per order. These restrictions may include orders placed by or under the same customer account, the same credit card, and/or orders that use the same billing and/or shipping address. In the event that we make a change to or cancel an order, we may attempt to notify you by contacting the e-mail and/or billing address/phone number provided at the time the order was made. We reserve the right to limit or prohibit orders that, in our sole judgment, appear to be placed by dealers, resellers or distributors.
        \n\nYou agree to provide current, complete and accurate purchase and account information for all purchases made at our store. You agree to promptly update your account and other information, including your email address and credit card numbers and expiration dates, so that we can complete your transactions and contact you as needed.\n\nFor more detail, please review our Returns Policy.
      \n\nSECTION 7 – OPTIONAL TOOLS\n\nWe may provide you with access to third-party tools over which we neither monitor nor have any control nor input.\n\nYou acknowledge and agree that we provide access to such tools ”as is” and “as available” without any warranties, representations or conditions of any kind and without any endorsement. We shall have no liability whatsoever arising from or relating to your use of optional third-party tools.
    \n\nAny use by you of optional tools offered through the site is entirely at your own risk and discretion and you should ensure that you are familiar with and approve of the terms on which tools are provided by the relevant third-party provider(s).\n\nWe may also, in the future, offer new services and/or features through the website (including, the release of new tools and resources). Such new features and/or services shall also be subject to these Terms of Service.\n\nSECTION 8 – THIRD-PARTY LINKS\n\nCertain content, products and services available via our Service may include materials from third-parties.
    \n\nThird-party links on this site may direct you to third-party websites that are not affiliated with us. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating the content or accuracy and we do not warrant and will not have any liability or responsibility for any third-party materials or websites, or for any other materials, products, or services of third-parties.\n\nWe are not liable for any harm or damages related to the purchase or use of goods, services, resources, content, or any other transactions made in connection with any third-party websites. Please review carefully the third-party’s policies and practices and make sure you understand them before you engage in any transaction. Complaints, claims, concerns, or questions regarding third-party products should be directed to the third-party.
    \n\nSECTION 9 – USER COMMENTS, FEEDBACK AND OTHER SUBMISSIONS\n\nIf, at our request, you send certain specific submissions (for example contest entries) or without a request from us you send creative ideas, suggestions, proposals, plans, or other materials, whether online, by email, by postal mail, or otherwise (collectively, ‘comments’), you agree that we may, at any time, without restriction, edit, copy, publish, distribute, translate and otherwise use in any medium any comments that you forward to us. We are and shall be under no obligation (1) to maintain any comments in confidence; (2) to pay compensation for any comments; or (3) to respond to any comments.
     \n\nWe may, but have no obligation to, monitor, edit or remove content that we determine in our sole discretion are unlawful, offensive, threatening, libelous, defamatory, pornographic, obscene or otherwise objectionable or violates any party’s intellectual property or these Terms of Service.
     \n\nYou agree that your comments will not violate any right of any third-party, including copyright, trademark, privacy, personality or other personal or proprietary right. You further agree that your comments will not contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, abusive or obscene material, or contain any computer virus or other malware that could in any way affect the operation of the Service or any related website. You may not use a false e-mail address, pretend to be someone other than yourself, or otherwise mislead us or third-parties as to the origin of any comments. You are solely responsible for any comments you make and their accuracy. We take no responsibility and assume no liability for any comments posted by you or any third-party.
      \n\nSECTION 10 – PERSONAL INFORMATION\n\nYour submission of personal information through the store is governed by our Privacy Policy. To view our Privacy Policy.\n\nSECTION 11 – ERRORS, INACCURACIES AND OMISSIONS\n\nOccasionally there may be information on our site or in the Service that contains typographical errors, inaccuracies or omissions that may relate to product descriptions, pricing, promotions, offers, product shipping charges, transit times and availability. We reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions, and to change or update information or cancel orders if any information in the Service or on any related website is inaccurate at any time without prior notice (including after you have submitted your order).\n\nYou agree that from time to time we may remove the service for indefinite periods of time or cancel the service at any time, without notice to you.
     \n\nWe undertake no obligation to update, amend or clarify information in the Service or on any related website, including without limitation, pricing information, except as required by law. No specified update or refresh date applied in the Service or on any related website, should be taken to indicate that all information in the Service or on any related website has been modified or updated.\n\n\nSECTION 12 – PROHIBITED USES\n\nWe do not warrant that the results that may be obtained from the use of the service will be accurate or reliable.
     \n\nSECTION 12 – DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES; LIMITATION OF LIABILITY\n\nWe do not guarantee, represent or warrant that your use of our service will be uninterrupted, timely, secure or error-free.
</string>

    <string name="help"></string>
    <string name="for_queries_ninfo_reyound_com">For queries:\ninfo@reyound.com</string>
    <string name="_90ft_road_mumbai_400017_nemail_info_reyound_com_nphone_91_7021931428">90ft Road, Mumbai, 400017\nEmail: info@reyound.com\nPhone: +91 7021931428</string>
    <string name="Overview"><b>Overview</b>\n\nLooking for men’s clothing that refuses to compromise on fit, comfort and style? Then look no further than Reyound. Our T-shirts are perfect for casual and regular wear. Available in a variety of colours and fabrics with innovative features like moisture-wicking and odour control, you’ll find our T-shirts work overtime to keep you comfortable and looking your best.\n\n
Comfy and Stretch. These T-Shirts are made of high-Quality cotton. Lightweight, Soft and breathable graphic Shirts will make you comfortable when you wear them at the home, office, regular or work out.
We have a special department for the strict quality inspection before shipment, ensure that no quality problems, just give delivery. If you have any comments or suggestions on our products or service, you can give us a message, we will give you the first time to reply! All of our products come with durable double stitching for more durability.\n\n<b>About Brand</b>\n\n Reyound is a manufacturer and marketer of everyday basic apparel. We sell multiple products like women and men tops wear and bottom wear. Reyound delivers the comfort, style, and performance to fit your active lifestyle. This tee is a wardrobe essential, offering both the style and comfort of cotton with the benefits of performance.</string>
    <string name="ok_text" />
    <string name="silver">Become a SILVER Membership SignIn the Reyound\n\n\n<b>BENEFITS OF SILVER MEMBERSHIP\n\n</b>Earn 15% Reyound Points on your link purchases\nEarn 2% Reyound Points from Refer and Earn friend circle</string>
    <string name="gold">Become a GOLD Member Monthly Purchase of \n₹5000 - ₹10,000.\n\n\n <b>BENEFITS OF GOLD MEMBERSHIP\n\n Earn 20% of Reyound Points\n on your link PurchaseEarn 3% Reyound Points fron friend circle Refer and Earn</b></string>
    <string name="platinum">Become a PLATINUM Member on monthly Personal Purchase of ₹10,000 and above.\n\n\n<b>BENEFITS OF PLATINUM\nMEMBERSHIP </b>\n\nEarn 25% Reyound Points on your link purchase</string>

    <string name="withdrawn">Total Withdrawn \n<b>₹ 8000</b></string>
    <string name="dummy_text">Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry\'s standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book. It has survived not only five centuries, but also the leap into electronic typesetting, remaining essentially unchanged. It was popularised in the 1960s with the release of Letraset sheets containing Lorem Ipsum passages, and more recently with desktop publishing software like Aldus PageMaker including versions of Lorem Ipsum. Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry\'s standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book. It has survived not only five centuries, but also the leap into electronic typesetting, remaining essentially unchanged. It was popularised in the 1960s with the release of Letraset sheets containing Lorem Ipsum passages, and more recently with desktop publishing software like Aldus PageMaker including versions of Lorem Ipsum.</string>
    <string name="size">Size: <b>xx-Large</b></string>
</resources>